(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T21:03:45.664359",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あぁ またやっちゃった
Oh, I messed up again.
隠してたわけじゃないの
It's not like I was hiding it.
きっとただ言ってないだけ
I just didn't mention it.
だって恥ずかしいんだもん
Because it's too embarrassing.
意外と寂しんぼ
I get surprisingly lonely.
意外と甘えんぼ
I am surprisingly spoiled.
あぁ まだやっちゃった
Ah, I messed up again...
隠してたわけじゃないの
It's not like I was hiding it,
きっとただ一点 愛だけだって
I'm sure it's just pure love,
恥ずかしいんだもん
It's just so embarrassing.
意外と寂しんぼ
Surprisingly lonely,
意外と甘えんぼ
surprisingly spoiled,
意外とあわてんぼ
surprisingly flustered,
意外と照れ屋
surprisingly shy.
丸い飛行雲
A round condensation trail,
飛び出したカップケーキ
a cupcake that popped out,
3回目コンディショナー
conditioning my hair for the third time,
余るパズル
an extra puzzle piece.
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢見心地
Floating lightly in a dreamy haze,
ひとつひとつ数えて おやすみなさい
counting them one by one, have a good night.
密かに芽生えたこの気持ち
This feeling that quietly sprouted—
真っ直ぐ見つめないで
don't stare at me so straight.
「なんだっけ…///」
"What was it again...///"
言葉にしちゃうと きっとそうじゃない
Putting it into words isn't quite right,
照れちゃうだけ おちゃらかしちゃうじゃない
I just get shy and try to play it off.
本当の本当は 隠したいんじゃないの
The truth is, it's not that I want to hide it—
もう そうじゃないのにさ
even though it's not like that anymore.
曖昧なんじゃない この気持ちは間違いじゃない
This feeling isn't vague at all, it's not wrong!
指切りげまん かなりドジっ子で
Pinky swear, I'm quite clumsy
優柔不断でも 絶対に毎日
and indecisive, but will you still come
会いに来てくれるよね？
and see me every day without fail?
本来臆病で 意外と泣き虫
I'm naturally timid and a bit of a crybaby,
全然変わらずに 元来君ばっかり！
never changing, it's always been all about you!
当たり前のように キュンしちゃう
Falling for you like it's the most natural thing,
君がいないと ガッカリしちゃう
without you, I feel so empty.
本当の本当に ショボリしちゃうわ
It really, really makes me so sad—
会いたくなっちゃうな
I want to see you now.
後悔ばっかりしちゃう この心も勇気出しちゃえ
I always regret it, but let's be brave this time!
この指止まれ
Land on this finger!
「言っちゃった…///」
"I said it...///"
もしかしたら運命かも 赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
Maybe this is destiny, maybe the red thread is visible,
本当の本当はバレてるのかも 目合わせられないかも
maybe my true feelings are showing, maybe I can't meet your eyes.
曖昧になんてない たくさん私を見てて！
It's not vague at all, look at me lots!
弱いところ気付かれたり 寂しさごと包まれたり
You see through my weaknesses, you hold me when I'm lonely,
いつでも笑い合ったり たまにはムッと言い合ったり
we always laugh together and sometimes get into little fights,
ずっとずっと傍にいて欲しい
but I want you by my side forever...
約束だぞ
That's a promise!
「言っちゃった…///」
"I said it...///"
もしかしたら運命かも 赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
Maybe this is destiny, maybe the red thread is visible,
本当の本当はバレてるのかも 目合わせられないかも
maybe my true feelings are showing, maybe I can't meet your eyes.
曖昧になんてない たくさん私を見てて！
It's not vague at all, look at me lots!
「いけた！」
"I did it!"
こんばんわっほーい！
Good evening, wah-hoy!
ほろらいぶ4期生 潤羽るし… あ、違う！角巻わためです！
Hololive 4th generation, Uruha L- ah, no! Tsunomaki Watame here!
みんな来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much for coming!
なんと1周年を迎えました！
We've somehow reached our 1st anniversary!
もうリハ頑張りすぎてヘトヘトなんだけど (笑)
I worked so hard in rehearsal I'm totally exhausted, haha!
頑張っていきたいなと思います。
But I want to keep doing my best.
そして今日はこっち！シャープ角巻わため1周年！
And today, here! Hashtag #TsunomakiWatame1stAnniversary!
こちらのハッシュタグでたくさんツイートしていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you could tweet lots using this hashtag!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
もう1発目は曖昧ショコラテだったんですけど、今日はどどどどどって歌いますよ！
My first song was "Aimai Chocolat," but today I'll be singing a whole bunch more!
いいですか？次の曲いきますよ！
Are you ready? Here comes the next song!
歌ってみた動画でも上げております。
I've also uploaded cover videos of it.
こういう場で初めて歌うかな？バブールラブ！
I wonder if I'm singing it for the first time in a venue like this? "Baburu Rabu!"
世界はなんて複雑なんですか
Why is the world so complicated?
秘密の言葉教えてほしい
Please teach me the secret words.
がんばれ私！いつも以上に
Do your best, me! Even more than usual,
今日も明日も世界は回る
today and tomorrow the world keeps turning.
今日も同じ日が来るなら
If today brings the same day again,
いつも以上にしなくちゃです
I've got to do even better than usual.
会話ってあぁ難しい
Conversation is, ah, so difficult;
なんでも伝わるのに不器用
so clumsy even though everything should get across.
何度も何度もがんばるのに
Even though I try over and over again,
できないこともあるかもなんて
there are things I still can't do, perhaps?
そこであきらめなければ
If you don't give up right there,
いつかはきっと君まで届くから
it will surely reach you someday.
文字ならどうしても単純になっちゃいそうな感情は
Emotions that would become simple in mere text—
内緒の魔法を唱えてほしい
I want you to chant a secret magic spell!
がんばれ私！時には大胆に今日も隣で世界を歩く
Do your best, me! Sometimes boldly walking through the world by your side today too.
実は怒ると怖かったり嫉妬したりしちゃいます、はい
Actually, I can get scary when angry, or get jealous, yes.
あぁいいな甘い魔法を見たこともないようなアイスクリーム
Ah, how nice, an ice cream like a sweet magic I've never seen before.
秘めた想いは時々ドキドキ溢れた言葉に真っ赤になって
My hidden feelings sometimes throb and turn bright red with overflowing words.
皆がいいとか上手く言えないけどそれでも一緒がいいな
I can't say things like "everyone is good," but even so, I want to be together.
言葉はなんでこんなにこんなに複雑なんですか
Why are words so, so complicated?
秘密の言葉教えてほしい
Please teach me the secret words.
がんばれ私！いつも以上に
Do your best, me! Even more than usual,
今日も明日も世界は回る
today and tomorrow the world keeps turning.
ずっとこれからも大好きなみんなと
Forever from now on, with everyone I love so much,
喧嘩したり仲直りしたりもっともっとそんな平穏が続いていけばいいな
fighting and making up, I hope such peaceful days continue more and more.
いいな文字だと単純になっちゃいそうな感情は内緒の魔法を唱えてほしい
It'd be nice if emotions that turn simple in text could have a secret magic spell chanted for them!
がんばれ私！時には大胆に今日も隣で世界を歩かせて
Do your best, me! Sometimes let me boldly walk through the world by your side today too.
世界はなんて美しいんですか
How beautiful the world is!
秘密の言葉教えてほしい
Please teach me the secret words.
がんばれ私！いつも以上に
Do your best, me! Even more than usual,
今日も明日も世界は回る
today and tomorrow the world keeps turning.
今日もみんなと世界を歩く
Today too, I walk through the world with everyone.
あー！イヤホンが外れちゃった！
Ah! My earphones came off!
イヤホン外れちゃった！
My earphones came off!
イヤホンないなった、片耳イヤホンないな
My earphones are gone—one-sided earphone is...
あっ、あった！
Ah, there it is!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ふー！
Whew!
危なかった、動きすぎたね最後ポロッと抜けてしまったな
That was close, I moved too much and it slipped right out at the end.
あ、でも歌中じゃなくてよかったね！はー
Ah, but I'm glad it wasn't in the middle of the song! Haah.
ああ、聴いてくれてありがとう。
Ah, thank you for listening.
これ歌ってみた動画も上げていて、あのみんなにもねすごい好きだよって言ってもらった曲だから
I uploaded a cover video of this too, and since everyone told me they really liked it,
1周年で持ってきました。
I brought it for my 1st anniversary.
聴いてくれてありがとう。
Thank you for listening.
次もみんなに、お求めのこの曲いいよって言われた曲です。このまま聴いてください。
Next is also a song that everyone asked for, a song people said is good. Please keep listening.
ハロ、ハワユ。
Hello, How Are You.
窓を開けて 小さく呟いた
I opened the window and whispered softly,
誰もいない 部屋で一人
Alone in a room where no one is there.
もう朝が来たよ 土砂降りの朝が
Morning has come, a pouring morning.
ティックタック 私のネジを 誰か巻いて
Tick-tock, someone wind my spring up.
昔のアニメに そんなのいたっけな
Was there a character like that in old anime?
羨ましいな 皆に愛されて
I'm envious, being loved by everyone.
馬鹿なこと言わないで 支度をしなくちゃ
Don't say stupid things, I have to get ready.
辛い涙の痕を隠すため
To hide the traces of painful tears,
もう口癖になった「まあいっか」
"Oh well" has already become my habit.
昨日の言葉がふと頭をよぎる
Yesterday's words suddenly cross my mind:
「もう君には全然期待してないから」
"I have no expectations for you anymore."
それもまあ 私だって
Well, even so, I myself
自分に期待などしてないけれど
Don't have any expectations for myself either,
アレは一体どういうつもりですか
But what on earth do you mean by that?
喉元まで出かかった言葉
Words that came up to my throat,
口をついて出たのは嘘
What slipped out of my mouth was a lie.
こうして今日も私は貴重な言葉を浪費して生きていく
And so today too, I live wasting precious words.
何故隠してしまうのですか
Why do I always end up hiding it?
笑われるのが怖いのですか
Is it because I'm afraid of being laughed at?
誰にも会いたくないのですか
Is it because I don't want to meet anyone?
それ本当ですか
Is that really true?
曖昧という名の海に溺れて 息もできないほど苦しいの
Drowning in a sea called ambiguity, it's so suffocating I can't breathe.
少し声が聞きたくなりました
I wanted to hear your voice a little.
本当に弱いな
I'm really weak, aren't I?
一向に進まない支度の途中 ぼろっとした頭で思う
In the middle of getting nowhere, I think with a messy head:
「もう理由を付けて休んでしまおうかな」
"Shall I just find a reason and take a break?"
いやいや分かってますって
No, no, I know, I know.
なんとなし言ってみただけだよ 分かってるから怒らないでよ
I was just saying it casually, I know so don't be angry.
幸せだろうと 不幸だろうと
Whether happy or unhappy,
平等に 残酷に 朝日は昇る
The morning sun rises equally and cruelly.
生きていくだけで精一杯の私に
For me, who is trying my best just to live,
これ以上何を望むというの
What more could I possibly wish for?
何故気にしてしまうのですか
Why do I mind it so much?
本当は愛されたいのですか
Do I really want to be loved?
その手を離したのは誰ですか
Who was it that let go of that hand?
気付いていますか
Do you realize it?
人生にタイムカードがあるなら
If life has a time card,
終わりの時間は何時なんだろう
What time would the end be?
私が生きた分の給料は 誰が払うんですか
Who pays the salary for the life I've lived?
サンキュー ありがとうって言いたいのに
Thank you, even though I want to say thank you,
サンキュー ありがとうって言いたいよ
Thank you, I want to say thank you.
サンキュー 一度だけでも良いから
Thank you, even if it's just once,
心の底から大泣きしながら ありがとうって言いたいのに
While crying my eyes out from the bottom of my heart, I want to say thank you.
ハロ ハワユ
Hello, how are you,
Hello, how are you...
設定を見直して、クソ雑魚回線を卒業したので、歌、歌います！行きます！
I reviewed my connection settings and graduated from trash-tier internet, so I'm gonna sing! Here I go!
回線の設定を見直して
I reviewed my connection settings
強々な回線になりました
and got a super strong connection!
もう絶対途切れ…
It will never drop aga—
えい、請求！
Hey, invoice!
おなかすいた おなかすいた
I'm so hungry, I'm so hungry
おいしいご飯が食べたいな
I want to eat a delicious meal
あとさきなんにも考えないで
Without thinking about what comes next,
たくさん食べたいな
I want to eat a lot
ここから遠の彼方 永久の止まらぬ
Far away from here, eternally unstopping...
ほらほら掲げ 叫べお前ら
Raise your hands and shout out, everyone!
いつかに見捨てた夢があるなら
If you have a dream you abandoned long ago,
迷わずしめと拾い集めよ
gather it up without hesitation.
ここから遠の彼方 永久の止まらぬ
Far away from here, eternally unstopping...
ほらほら掲げ 叫べお前ら
Raise your hands and shout out, everyone!
いつかに見捨てた夢があるなら
If you have a dream you abandoned long ago,
迷わずしめと拾い集めよ
gather it up without hesitation.
すべて見落とすくらいなら
If I'm going to overlook everything,
いっそ夢物語でいいから
I'd rather it be just a dream story.
例えばよく晴れた曇り空
For instance, a partly cloudy sky that cleared up well,
キャンバスに見立てて思い描いた
painted on a canvas as I imagined
君の笑顔
your smiling face.
今は辛くても がむしゃらに叫んだ日々が
Even if it's tough now, the days I cried out recklessly
雲を破りやがて一筋の光
will break through the clouds into a single ray of light
差し込んでくる
shining down.
青空の下で また君と
Beneath the blue sky, with you once again...
出会いたい
I want to meet.
曇天羊
Cloudy Sheep
俺んとこ来ないか？
Wanna come to my place?
ワンナイト・カーニバル 胸の奥zuki-zukiと音立てるAngel
One night carnival, my heart is throbbing loudly, Angel
とにかくもう 行儀よく真面目なんてうんざりだった
Either way, being polite and diligent was getting tedious, Angel
ワンナイト・カーニバル
One night carnival
みんなも一緒に！
Everyone together!
退屈に怯えてたのさ 夜の闇に逃げ込んだAngel
Afraid of boredom, we escaped into the night's darkness, Angel
捨て猫みたいなおれ達に 帰る場所なんてもうどこにもなかった
Just like stray cats, we no longer had anywhere to return to, Angel
Can you master baby? master baby!
master baby! master baby!
master baby! be my baby!
Can you master baby? so long...
瞬きもせず 俺達は光の渦に巻き込まれてく
In the blink of an eye, we were sucked into a whirlpool of light
雲の隙間に 照らせ 青白き月よ 照らせ
Shine out from between the clouds, pallid moon, shine out
星が瞬くdistance さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
Stars sparkling in the distance, the legend of lonely people
one night carnival fun fun
風に香るtacticsが俺の胸を締め付けるAngel
Your fragrant tactics riding on the wind press hard upon my heart, Angel
焼けたアスファルトに打った鼓動を確実に俺達は聴いたんだ
We could definitely hear the beat drummed out on the baked asphalt, Angel
Can you master baby? master baby!
master baby! master baby!
master baby! so long...
俺んところこないか？
Won't you come with me?
ワンナイト・カーニバル
One Night Carnival
胸の奥Zuki-Zukiと音立てる
My heart beats with a throbbing ache deep inside,
「とにもかくにも 行儀良く真面目なんてうんざりだった」
“Anyway, being well-behaved and serious was such a drag.”
退屈に怯えてたのさ
Frightened by the boredom,
夜の闇に逃げ込んだ
I slipped away into the night's darkness.
「捨て猫みたいな俺達に 帰る場所なんてもう何処にも無かった」
“For strays like us, we had nowhere left to return to.”
Can you master baby? master baby!
Can't you master baby? master baby!
Can't you master baby? so long...
瞬きもせずに 俺達は光の渦に巻き込まれていく 雲の隙間に
Without blinking, we get swallowed up in a vortex of light through the clouds.
照らせ 青白き月よ
Illuminate us, pale blue moon.
照らせ 星が瞬くDistance
Illuminate the distance where stars twinkle.
さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
It's the legend of the lonely ones,
One Night Carnival fun fun
恋しているのさ
I'm in love...
この夜に恋しているのさ
I'm in love with this night,
やがて 海が見える
before long, the sea comes into view.
さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
It's the legend of the lonely ones.
One Night Carnival fun fun
「あの頃の俺達 闇の中じゃなくちゃ夢見られなかった」
“Back then, we couldn't dream unless we were in the darkness.”
「あのミラーボールみたいに 明るくて円満な御殿に憧れただけさ 行こうぜピリオドの向こうへ…」
“We just yearned for a bright, harmonious palace like that mirrorball. Let's go beyond the period...”
もうすぐ 海が見える
Soon the sea will be in view,
さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
the legend of the lonely ones.
One Night Carnival fun fun
もうすぐ 海が見える
Soon the sea will be in view,
さみしがり屋達の伝説さ
the legend of the lonely ones.
One Night Carnival fun fun
One Night Carnival roll
Let's get free...
イェーイ！ 最高のワンナイト・カーニバルだったよなぁ！
Yeah! That was the ultimate One Night Carnival, wasn't it?!
あとステージが これナイト・ミィーバーのステージに変わりました！
And the stage has transformed into the Night Fever stage!
そして 後ろにはキリコ・キュービィの車体ちょっと今日は お辞儀しております！
And behind us, Kiriko Cuuby's vehicle... we're bowing today!
あ、一緒の後ろ向いちゃうんだね。お辞儀しております！
Ah, we're turning around together, huh? We're bowing!
あとさっきのワンナイト・カーニバルなんだけど、コーラスをある方々に あの、お願いしまして誰か分かったかな？ 分かったかな？
And for that One Night Carnival earlier, I asked certain people to do the chorus... I wonder if anyone figured out who they were? Did you figure it out?
声だいぶ特徴あったと思うけど、
Their voices were pretty distinctive, I think,
実は ごきげんのみんなにお願いしました！ ポルカちゃん、ねねちゃん、らみちゃん、ししろん、ありがとうございます！ ありがとうございます！
but actually, I asked the Gokigen crew! Polka-chan, Nene-chan, Lamy-chan, Shishiron, thank you so much! Thank you very much!
そして 次の曲は バカたれ共と共にコーラスをお願いしておりまーす！ ちょっと水飲んでもいい？ お水いただきまして、
And for the next song, I've asked the Bakatare trio to join in on the chorus! Is it alright if I have some water? I'll have some water.
くぅー！染みるぅ！染みわたるー！ ありがとうございます！
Ahh! So refreshing! It soaks right in! Thank you!
では行きましょう！ 次の曲みんなもダンスするんだぞー！ キングゲイナー！
Now let's go! For the next song, everyone's gonna dance too! King Gainer!
キング キング キングゲイナー メタル・オーバーマン キングゲイナー
King, King, King Gainer, Metal Overman, King Gainer!
真白な地平の向こうから あいつの影が俺を呼んだんだ
From beyond the pure white horizon, that shadow called out to me.
こもるだけでは何ができるといじける俺に教えてくれた
You taught a hesitant me, who thought staying cooped up was all I could do.
何ができると いじける俺に教えてくれた
You taught my timid self what I could do,
君と出会って胸を合わせば命が
When I met you and our hearts aligned, my life—
メタル・ファイアー 燃えてきた
Metal Fire, starts burning,
メタル・フルコート
Metal Full Coat!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance!
キングゲイナー
King Gainer,
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer!
愛と勇気は言葉感じられれば力
Love and courage are power if you feel them in words,
キング キング キングゲイナー 探すのさ今ここで
King, king, King Gainer, searching right here now!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
探すのさ今ここで
searching right here now!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
メタル・オーバーマン キングゲイナー
Metal Overman King Gainer!
ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance, dance!
シック・ボディ！ シック・ボディ！
Sick body! Sick body!
イェイ！イェイ！イェイ！イェイ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
今日は足りないだぞ お互い！
It's still not enough for us today!
いいね みんなダンスありがとう！
Awesome, thank you all for dancing!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer!
凍てつく空気を切り裂いて奴に遅れず飛んで見せたい
Tearing through the frozen air, I want to show I can fly to keep up,
明日という日覗きたいからおじける俺を忘れるために
To peek at tomorrow and forget my timid self,
抱かせてくれよお前の心命を
Let me embrace your heart and your life...
メタル・ファイアー 愛してる
Metal Fire, I love you,
メタル・フルコート
Metal Full Coat!
愛と勇気は口だけの事とわかれば求め合いえ…
Knowing love and courage are just words, we seek each other...
みんな一緒に！
Everyone together!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
Dance, dance, dance, dance!
ひとりだけではいやだお前だけでも無理だ
I don't want to be alone, nor can I do it with just you,
お前だけでも無理だ
nor can you do it alone.
愛と勇気は言葉感じられれば力
Love and courage are power if you can feel them in words,
感じられれば力
power you can feel in words.
ひとりだけではいやだ お前だけでも無理だ
I don't want to be alone, nor can I do it with just you,
お前だけでも無理だ
nor can you do it alone.
愛と勇気は言葉感じられれば力
Love and courage are power if you can feel them in words,
感じられれば力
power you can feel in words.
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
探すのさ今ここで
searching right here now!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
メタル・オーバーマン キングゲイナー
Metal Overman King Gainer!
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer!
今かけるこの命
Now betting this life...
キング キング キングゲイナー
King, king, King Gainer,
メタル・オーバーマン キングゲイナー
Metal Overman King Gainer!
ふー！ハハハ！あったりー！
Woo! Haha! Exactly!
水飲んでもいいですか？
Can I drink some water?
これリハでさ、ずっと歌ってたらさ、もう力尽きちゃってさ。
I kept singing during rehearsal and totally ran out of energy.
うめー！
Delicious!
そして、残念ながら、あの後ろのヤクザさんとはここでお別れになります。
And unfortunately, it's time to say goodbye to the yakuza guys in the back.
一緒に水飲んでこれてありがとー！
Thanks for drinking water with me!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
ありがとうね 一緒に踊ってくれてありがとう
Thank you so much for dancing along with me!
すっー すっと消えていく
Fading away smoothly...
ありがとう みんなも一緒に踊ってくれたり、あのキ、キ、キングギョーナって言ってくれて
Thank you everyone for dancing along with me, and calling me "King Gyo-na"!
ありがとう！とっても楽しかったぜ！
Thank you! I had so much fun!
次もみんなに、あの意外と「この曲合うかも」って言ってもらった曲を歌いたいなと思います。
Next, I'd like to sing a song that people told me, "You know, this song might suit you unexpectedly well."
吉原ラメント
Yoshiwara Lament
江戸の町は今日も深く
The streets of Edo are deep today,
夜の帳かけてゆく
casting the veil of night.
鏡向いて 紅を引いて
Facing the mirror, applying rouge,
応じるまま 受け入れるまま
accepting and yielding as asked.
橙輝いていた花
The orange flowers that shone bright,
憧れてた 望んでいた
I yearned for them, I wished for them.
いつの間にか藍色の花
Before I knew it, blue flowers,
けどうち 安くないわ
but I am not cheap.
「誠はただ一人の何方かのためだけに咲いていたものだったけれども
"The truth is, it was meant to blossom solely for one special someone,
運命はわっちの自由を奪い そいであたしゃ歯車を回していくのでありんす」
but fate stole my freedom away and turned the gears instead, that's how it goes."
偽りだらけの恋愛 そして私を抱くのね
A romance full of falsehoods, and so you hold me in your arms.
悲しいくらいに感じたふりの吉原 今日は雨
Yoshiwara today is rain, feigning a sorrow so deep I feel it.
貴方様 どうか私を 買っていただけないでしょうか
My lord, won't you please buy me?
咲き出す 傘の群れに 濡れる 私は 雨
Blossoming in a crowd of umbrellas, getting wet in the rain, I am the rain.
行き交う群れ 賑わう声が ひしめき合い もつれ合い
The passing crowds, the bustling voices jostle and tangle together.
願うことは どうかいつか 鳥籠の外 連れ出して
I wish that someday, you would take me out of this birdcage.
「誠は行くあてなどなくなってしまいなのでしたのだけれども
"The truth is, I had nowhere else to go,
あなたの顔の中から見える景色だけは まちをいつなる時も癒やして呉れるのであるきす」
but the scenery seen from within your face always heals me, no matter when."
偽りだらけの恋愛 そして私を買うのね
A romance full of falsehoods, and so you buy me.
私に咲いた花びら 濡れる心に降るは 雨
Petals blooming upon me, falling upon my wet heart is the rain.
貴方様 どうか私と 一夜限りのたむれを
My lord, won't you share a night of fleeting play with me?
望む シミの数が 鈍く 心に 刺さる
Desiring, the number of stains dully pierce my heart.
恋人ごっこの夜に 吐息「あっあっ」と言わせて
In this night of lovers' play, making me let out gasps...
悲しいくらいに感じたふりの吉原 今日も雨
Yoshiwara today is rain once more, feigning a sorrow so deep I feel it.
偽りだらけの恋愛 そして私を抱くのね
A romance full of falsehoods, and so you hold me in your arms.
悲しいくらいに感じたふりの吉原 今日は雨
Yoshiwara today is rain, feigning a sorrow so deep I feel it.
貴方様 どうか私を 買っていただけないでしょうか
My lord, won't you please buy me?
咲き出す 傘の群れに 濡れる 私は 雨
Blossoming in a crowd of umbrellas, getting wet in the rain, I am the rain.
行き交う群れ 賑わう声が ひしめき合い もつれ合い
The passing crowds, the bustling voices jostle and tangle together.
願うことは どうかいつか 鳥籠の外 連れ出して
I wish that someday, you would take me out of this birdcage.
「誠は行くあてなどなくなってしまいなのでしたのだけれども...」
"The truth is, I had nowhere else to go..."
偽りだらけの恋愛 そして私を買うのね
A romance full of falsehoods, and so you buy me.
私に咲いた花びら 濡れる心に降るは 雨
Petals blooming upon me, falling upon my wet heart is the rain.
ありがとうございました！やっぱこういうのが記念の場所だとなんか
Thank you very much! Somehow, having this kind of thing at a commemorative venue...
緊張すんね 水飲んでいいですか？
makes me so nervous. Can I drink some water?
いや、次の曲がね、大変なもんでね
Man, the next song is so tough, you see...
あ！今、今ちょっと、不誤って音が入ってしまいましたが、すみませんでした！
Ah! I accidentally made some weird noise just now, I'm so sorry!
いや、次、次がね、もうね
And the next, next one is already...
すごいよ
It's amazing!
すごいですよ
It really is!
頑張りますよ
I'll do my best!
じゃあ行きましょうか
Well then, shall we go?
もう一番盛り上がるところだと思って行ってもいい！
Even if you think this is the peak, go for it!
最高に盛り上がってください！たくさんコメントもください！
Get as hyped as possible! And give me lots of comments!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
エルエルエル！
L・L・L!
Don't you give me your love and passion?
Let's ride to hell, 追従してGo
Let's ride to hell, following on—Go!
一緒なら寧ろ死にたいじゃない
Wouldn't you rather die together?
Beyond the line 果てなんかない
Beyond the line, with no end in sight,
I swear, I'm gonna be so fxxking grateful
I swear, I'm gonna be so fucking grateful.
Blessing word 貴方は至高
Blessing word, you are supreme.
命令に Your highness 忠実にFollow
Following your commands, Your highness,
You give orders 渡しはしない 何より尊いものを
You give orders, I won't let anyone take my most precious treasure.
You don't know why my love is crying
凝着したい 過剰なくらい
I want to cling to you, excessively so.
永遠(とわ)になりたい don't wanna cry
I want it to last forever, don't wanna cry.
嫉妬妄想狂いそうよ
Jealousy and delusions are driving me crazy.
Don't you give me your love and passion?
愛とは暴動衝動 Let go
Love is a riot and impulse, Let go.
精神以上に本能、心臓まで More 要求したい
More than the mind, my instincts, even my heart want more.
I don't want to live in a world without you
貴方以外のこの未来を kill it, kill it
Kill it, kill it, any future without you.
I would be happy to kill it for my love
go till the end 視線は Lock
Go till the end, my gaze is locked.
go to the end 視線は Lock
Go to the end, my gaze is locked.
遮られずに遂げたい願い
A wish I want to fulfill without interruption.
straight to you 純心は Fly
Straight to you, pure heart takes flight.
above the star and sun… so fxxking wonderful
Above the star and sun... so fucking wonderful.
hey, get out 冗談じゃない
Hey, get out, I'm not joking.
視界の dirty は排除して trash
Clear away the dirty from my sight, trash.
kick them out 容赦 など無い
Kick them out, with no mercy.
誰より譲れぬ存在を
Someone more irreplaceable than anyone.
i'm in the dark, can't see your eyes
暗い 見え ない 孤独 は 痛い
The dark, unseen solitude is painful.
共に 居 たい no more time！
I want to be together, no more time!
窒息 もう 苦しい よ
Suffocating, it hurts so much.
won't you come and hold me tight
愛 とは 情情 結晶 get all
Love is the crystallization of passion, get all.
想像 以上の 恩情、 hard な 応え 要請 してる
Demanding a hard response of affection beyond imagination.
i wanna make it with you, baby
貴方の愛を得られるなら risk it, risk it
If I can have your love, risk it, risk it.
i'm gonna risk it all what's for two of us
狂う 愛憎 模様 marble に 溶かして
Melting the crazy love-hate pattern into marble.
1(one) and all、融合 焦燥 さえも 形状 は 悲壮 自由に 細胞 単位 で
One and all, even fusion and impatience, tragic forms freely in cellular units.
you don't know why my love is crying
凝着したい 過剰なくらい
I want to cling to you, excessively so.
12細胞 単位で
In twelve cellular units.
you don't know why my love is crying
凝着したい 過剰なくらい
I want to cling to you, excessively so.
永遠になりたい don't wanna cry
I want it to last forever, don't wanna cry.
抱きしめてよ もっと
Hold me tighter!
Don't you give me your love and passion?
貴方のすべて頂戴
Give me everything you are.
理由なんていらない ただ愛し合ってたい
I don't need a reason, I just want us to love each other.
i don't want to live in a world without you
貴方以外 何もいらない
I don't need anything except you.
get it, get it
i can't resist it, get it for my love
i'll spend my life for loving you
kill it, kill it
i'm imaging now, if you're mine, it's like a paradise and haven and more
I'm imagining now, if you're mine, it's like a paradise and haven and more.
you're the only man who i love, in my life and destiny and all
Don't you give me your love and passion?
i know the border. it should be wrecked, go
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
お水飲みます！
I'm going to drink some water!
お水、お水
Water, water.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いやこれ、これリハでめっちゃ歌ってさ
Man, I practiced singing this so much in rehearsal,
２回リハで全力で歌ってさ、もうヘトヘトなんじゃが
sang it with all my might twice during rehearsal, so I'm totally exhausted,
なんとか歌えてよかったです。どう？楽しかった？かっこよかった？
but I'm glad I managed to sing it. How was it? Was it fun? Was it cool?
はーい！実はこの後もまだありますんで
Yeah! Actually, there's still more coming up after this,
ありますんでこのまま見てってください。ビックニュースもありますんで
so please keep watching. There's also big news coming up,
バツカジッパありがとう！
Batsu-Kajippa, thank you!
スーパーチャットもね、メンバーシップも本当にありがとうございます。見えてますよ、ありがとう！では...
Thank you so much for the Super Chats and memberships too! I can see them, thank you! Now then...
なんかね、今日ね
You know, today...
あのホロライブENのね
...from Hololive EN,
カリオペちゃんからメッセージをいただいたおります。
we received a message from Calliope-chan.
メッセージ、どうぞ！
Here's the message!
こんにちは！おっ、カリオペ・モリスです。
Konnichiwa! It's Mori Calliope.
わたみ先輩、一周年おめでとうございます！
Watame-senpai, happy 1st anniversary!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こういうレベル特別な曲に誘ってくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for inviting me to be part of such a special song.
今回はね、素晴らしい曲になりましたね！すごい！
It turned out to be such an amazing song! Awesome!
本当に本当に良かったです。
It was truly, truly wonderful.
わたみ先輩の声が大好きなので、至極恋です。
I love Watame-senpai's voice so much, I'm head over heels!
イエーイ！
Yay!
これからもよろしくお願いします。またいつか誘ってくださいね。
Looking forward to working with you more. Please invite me again sometime!
またいつかさあ、あの、何か作りたいと思いますね。一緒に、うんうんうん、イエーイ！
And hopefully we can make something together again someday. Together, yeah... Yay!
Let's make a nice song together again someday.
Thank you so much for inviting me and congrats on one year anniversary! Woo! Yay!
あと、うん、Thank you so much and おめでとうございます！
Anyway, um, thank you so much and omedetou gozaimasu!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ここからはちょっと喋らしてもらってもいいですか？
Do you mind if I talk a bit more from here?
そう、なんとカリオペちゃんからメッセージをいただいたのも
That's right, we even got a message from Calliope-chan,
なんとなんとこの後、21時15分9時15分PM 9:15から？
and what's more, starting right after this at 9:15 PM...
なんとカリオペちゃんとコラボをした！カリオペちゃん色々ありがとう！ありがとう、なんとコラボをしまして、
...we did a collab with Calliope-chan! Calliope-chan, thank you so much for everything! Thank you, we collaborated,
しかもどんてん羊をフィートカリオペちゃんでフル作成いたしまして、
and what's more, we made a full version of "Cloudy Sheep" featuring Calliope-chan!
この後9時15分から動画が上がります！サムネかっこいい！しかもあのダンスPVとなっておりまして、あのダンスをねちょっと頑張らせてもらって、そう撮影してそれをかっこいい動画にしていただいたので
The video goes up after 9:15! The thumbnail looks so cool! Plus, it's a dance PV, so I worked really hard on the dancing, we filmed it, and they turned it into such a cool video,
ぜひこの後9時15分動画を見て頂きたいなと思います。プレミア公開するので
so I really want you all to check out the video at 9:15. We're doing a premiere,
お願いします！たぶんね概要欄とかにねこの後記載して来れると思うんだけど見てね！
so please check it out! It should be linked in the description box afterwards, so take a look!
どんてん羊オリジナル、生唾フィートカリオペです！お願いします。そして1週、1週間じゃない、間違えた。1周年と言えば、みんな出してるあれがあるよな、記念のアレがよ！
"Cloudy Sheep" original, featuring Calliope! Please check it out. And for 1st... wait, not 1 week, my bad. Speaking of 1st anniversary, you know there's that thing everyone releases—that commemorative thing!
記念グッズ？わお！
Anniversary merch? Whoa!
活動一周年の記念グッズ！ふーみママ書き下ろしラバーマット、「わためNight Fever!!」ストーンコースター、あ、なんだっけ？角巻わためファースト…なんだ？あ、なんだなんだ！えっ、これなんだ？ちょっとあとで説明、説明するからよ、順番に行こう。
1st anniversary merch! Fuumi-mama's newly illustrated rubber mat, the "Watame Night Fever!!" stone coaster, oh, what was it? Tsunomaki Watame 1st... what? Oh, what is this?! Eh, what is this? I'll explain later, so let's go in order.
では、画像をお願いします。
Now, please bring up the image.
じゃじゃーん！ふーみ先生書き下ろしラバーマット！いや、これさ、あの、多分ビッグサイズで見たら分かるんじゃないかな。なんか、はいって…ない…ので、は？あれ？これ、下…入って…ますかね？
Ta-da! Fuumi-sensei's newly illustrated rubber mat! Man, if you see this in big size, you'll probably get it. Wait, it's not... in... so, wait? Huh? Is this... at the bottom... included?
ふーみママに聞いたらね、なんのことって言ってた。え、なんのことってとぼけてたけどね（笑）。
When I asked Fuumi-mama, she was like, "What are you talking about?" Eh, she played dumb like "What do you mean?" (laughs).
そう、ラバーマット、ラバーマットっていうのは、机の上とかに敷くちょっとでっかいサイズの、サイズも変えてあったと思うんだけど、敷けるマットになっております。
Yeah, the rubber mat—rubber mats are fairly large mats you put on your desk, and I think we even changed the size for this, so it's a mat you can lay down.
で、わためNight Fever!!ストーンコースター！あの、コースターね、ちょっとまた別バージョンで、既存図じゃないんだけど、ちょっと別バージョンで作っていただいたので、これも一緒に叩きます。あと特典がありまして、
And the "Watame Night Fever!!" stone coaster! The coaster was made in a slightly different version—not existing art, but a custom version—so we'll tap on this together too. And there's a bonus!
そう、入ってない、ざわざわ、ざわざ、ざわざわ、画像お願いします。特典がね、あるんですよ。
Yeah, it's not in there, murmur murmur... Please show the image. There's a bonus.
ばだーん！ふーみママ書き下ろし、角巻わため箔押し複製サイン入りイラストポストカード！これがさっきのラバーマットで両目が開いてたと思うんだけど、あの、ウインクしてあります、こっち。ウインクさせてもらいました。
Ta-da! Fuumi-mama's newly illustrated illustration postcard with Tsunomaki Watame's foil-stamped replica signature! In the rubber mat earlier both eyes were open, but on this one, she's winking. I had her wink.
いやいやいや、あと特典ボイス1種、あ、なんだっけ？なんたら、なんたら制作費は、あ？わためめのね、ボイスもついてきます。じゃあ本命
No no no, also bonus voice track 1, uh, what was it? Something production cost... ah, Watame's voice comes with it too. Now, the main...
ねえ 行きましょうか 画像をお願いします
Well, shall we go? Please show the image.
角巻わため ファーストアルバム 『わためうた』 vol.1！
Tsunomaki Watame's 1st album, "Watame no Uta Vol. 1"!
これはでっかくなっちゃったな ホロライブ4期生角巻わための1年間の奇跡を詰め込んだ集大成のファーストアルバムです
It ended up being quite big! It's a miraculous first album packed with a year's worth of Tsunomaki Watame's journey.
もう本当に ギリギリのギリギリで あのね グッズとか制作版の方とかにも もうめちゃくちゃお世話になりまして 今もなお多分お世話になってると思うんだけど 本当にありがとうございます！
Really, right down to the wire... I owe so much to the goods and production teams. Thank you truly so much!
夢が一つまた叶いました ありがとうございます 本当に！
Another dream has come true. Thank you so much! Truly!
本当にこうやって配信できるのもね 今 あの 動いてくださっているね スタジオで頑張ってくださってる方のおかげでもあるので 運営さん本当にありがと マネちゃんもありがと ふみママもありがと けみぱぱも けみぱぱもありがと
The fact that I can stream like this now is thanks to everyone working hard in the studio, management, Mane-chan, Fumi-mama, Kemi-papa...
よじさんありがと わためいともありがと～！ みんなの応援があったから形になりました
Yoji-san, and Watameito too! It became a reality because of everyone's support.
ふう……あかん 泣いたらあかん
Phew... No, I mustn't cry.
なんと クソ雑魚回線癖の ま ちょこちょこと作ってきた曲とか あいまいチョコレートとか 番犬羊とか で どんでんしつじとか あとスペシャル・トラックの なんとついていきます 1曲
And amazingly, it comes with one track of the songs I've made bit by bit, like "Kusozako Kaisei Kuse no Uta", "Aimai Chocolate", "Banken Hitsuji", and a Special Track!
よかったら 全部セットですと買えないんだけど 特典という形なんだけど 夢が叶えましたので よかったら買ってほしいなと思います
If you'd like, you can't buy it with the all-in-one set, but as a bonus perk, my dream has come true, so I'd love for you to buy it if you can.
あと ボリューム1っていうのも ボリューム2出せたらいいなっていう思いを込めて ボリューム1をつけました
Also, I put "Volume 1" with the hope that if I can release a Volume 2, that would be great.
いやあ 夢を叶える羊じゃい！ これからも夢をどんどん叶えていきたいと思いますので
Man, I'm a sheep who makes dreams come true! I want to keep making dreams come true from now on,
応援をよろしくお願いしまーす！
so I'd appreciate your continued support!
いやー やっと言えたよ！ やっと言えた 匂わせないように頑張った ずっと言えた こちらこそありがとだよ
Man, I could finally say it! I finally said it. I tried hard not to drop hints. Thank you so much as well!
みんながね こうやって応援してくれてるおかげで形になりました CDだよ！
It became a reality thanks to everyone supporting me like this. It's a CD!
来年2も出したいですね だから2年目もどうぞよろしくお願いします！ 一生懸命ボイトレも頑張ります！ ダンスも頑張ります！配信も頑張ります！よろしくお願いします！
I'd love to release a Volume 2 next year. So please treat me well in my second year too! I'll work hard on voice training, dancing, and streaming!
で なんとこの後ですね カリオペちゃんと一緒に歌わせてもらう 「ドンテン羊」歌わせてもらおうかなって いやここで歌って、も動画見てよ！
And amazingly, after this, I'm thinking of having you listen to "Donten Hitsuji", which I got to sing together with Calliope-chan... Well, even if I sing it here, please go watch the video!
頼むよ！ダンス頑張ったんだから動画も見てよ！ じゃあ先行で聞かせてもらいたいなと思います ドンテン羊 角巻わため feat. カリオペ、聞いてください
I'm begging you! I worked hard on the dancing, so please watch the video too! Well then, I'd like you to listen to a sneak peek. "Donten Hitsuji" by Tsunomaki Watame feat. Calliope, please listen.
たとえ良く晴れた曇り空 キャンバスに仕立てて 今ボクは何を描こう
Even if I tailor a brightly cleared cloudy sky onto a canvas, what shall I draw right now?
Yeah, watchish, Shishida start, ken-shiki, Callishi, shishida start
おろしたての靴で走り出す 見向きも呼べぬけもの 汚れてしまうことを恐れてちゃ どこにも行けないんだってね
Running out in brand-new shoes, a beast that can't even be glanced at—if you're afraid of getting dirty, you won't be able to go anywhere.
良くない！天気に顔伏せ歩いて すべて見落とすくらいなら いっそ夢物語でいいから
No good! If you're going to walk with your face down at the weather and miss everything, then I'd rather it just be a dream-like story!
たとえ良く晴れた曇り空 キャンバスに仕立てて思いを描いた 君の笑顔 今辛くても
Even if I tailor a brightly cleared cloudy sky onto a canvas and portray your smiling face... even if it's painful right now,
がむしゃらに叫んだ日々が 雲を破りやがて一筋の光 差し込んでくる
the days I shouted recklessly will tear through the clouds, and soon a single ray of light will shine through.
あおぞらの下で また君と
Beneath the blue sky, once again with you—
振り返れば 全ての思い出が 色鮮やかとは呼べない 涙で滲み ボロボロになってる
Looking back, all those memories cannot be called vivid; blurred by tears, they've become tattered.
ページがいくつも
With so many pages...
例えばよく晴れた曇り空
For instance, under a sunny yet cloudy sky,
take it right back to the start of it all
the part of me that knows the higher they fly, the harder they fall
is callin’ out to me, finally,
Is calling out to me, finally,
say goodbye to the friendless and shy once-upon-a-time “me”
say goodbye to the friendless and shy once-upon-a-time "me".
おろしたての靴で走り出す
Running out in freshly polished shoes,
道とも呼べぬ獣道
on an untamed animal path that can hardly be called a road.
汚れてしまうことを恐れてちゃ どこにも行けないんだって、ねえ
If we're afraid of getting dirty, we can't go anywhere, right?
よくない 天気に 顔 を 伏せ 歩いて
Walking with my head down in bad weather,
すべて 見落とす くらい なら
if I'm going to miss everything,
いっそ 夢物語 で 良い から
I'd rather it just be a fairy tale instead.
an endless expanse of sky has been here all along,
same song in my heart, no fear be it low or high,
this time do or die written in the sky,
the story that starts with you and i
美しい絵の具があれば どんな高いペンがあれば
If I had beautiful paints, if I had expensive pens,
世界で一番の絵が描けるって？
could I draw the best picture in the world?
そんなわけないから
There's no way that's true.
ひとつ、ふたつ、またひとつ線を描いた
One, two, and another line drawn—
少し、また少しずつ増えていって i’m not gonna run away
increasing little by little, I'm not gonna run away.
景色が、face to the sun, burn out the pain
The scenery, face to the sun, burn out the pain,
君と居た景色が find the scene that we saw that day
the scenery of being with you, find the scene that we saw that day,
僕が好きな、all the colors that follow rain . . .
all the colors that follow rain that I love...
一番好きな色 二度と会えない日が来たとしても
Even if a day comes when I can never see my favorite color again,
少しでも長く覚えていたい
I want to remember it for as long as possible.
君と居た日、その歌声、全部、全部
The days spent with you, that singing voice, all of it, all of it
夢物語じゃないから
is not just a fairy tale.
例えばよく晴れた 曇り空
For instance, under a sunny yet cloudy sky,
キャンバスに見立てて 思い描い た 君 の 笑顔
picturing a canvas, the smile of you I imagined.
今 は 辛く て も がむしゃらに 叫んだ 日々 が
Even if it's hard now, the days we recklessly cried out
雲 を 破りゃって 一筋 の 光 、差し込んでくる
will pierce the clouds as a single ray of light shines through,
青空 の 下 で また 君 と …
and under the blue sky, once again with you...
振り返ればすべての思い出が鮮やかとは呼べない
Looking back, not all memories can be called vivid;
涙でにじみボロボロになっているページがいくつもあるよ
there are pages blurred by tears and worn out to tatters.
take it right back to the start of it all
the part of me that knows the higher they fly, the harder they fall
is callin’ out to me, finally,
Is calling out to me, finally.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はあ、もうやり切ったよお！
Haah, I gave it my all!
みんな聞いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for listening!
あと、わためいとのみんな！来てくれてありがとう！駆けつけてくれていつもありがとうね。支えられて今本当にありがとう。
Also, thank you all for coming and supporting me!
この時間を開けてくれたホロメンのみんなもありがとう！先輩も後輩も、同期も、みんなありがとう！
Thank you also to all the holomem who made time for this!
今回、みんな忙しいかなと思って、同期にはちょっと声をかけるのを遠慮してしまったんだけど、次はあの声をかけようと思います（笑）
I hesitated to reach out this time, but next time I'll ask!
本当に、ごきげんのみんなも、わかたれどもも、コーラス時間取って録音してくれてありがとう。
Thank you to everyone in Gokigen and Wakataredomo for the chorus.
みんなありがとう、本当に。
Thank you everyone, truly.
このあと、9時15分からプレミアム公開があります！カリオペちゃんもありがとうね、ダンスも歌も頑張りました。よかったらプレミアム公開見てください、お願いします！
There's a premiere at 9:15! Please check it out!
そして、グッズ、ラバーマット、あとこうした特典ボイス、なんて言ってもアルバム！ ちょっと、あの1枚別々にはできなかったんだけど、あの丸っとね買ってもらえたらすごく嬉しいなと思います。
I'd be so happy if you could buy the whole album set.
そして、その買ってくれたものを勝手に、買ってくれたみんなの気持ちを勝手に、来年ますます頑張って夢を叶えていきたいなと思いますので、どうぞよろしくお願いいたします！
I'll work harder next year to make dreams come true!
これで一周年迎えられたのもみんなのおかげです！ありがとうございました！ありがとう！またねー！
Thank you everyone for a wonderful 1st anniversary!
角巻わため 3D 1st Anniversary Live Fever!!
[Tsunomaki Watame 3D 1st Anniversary Live Fever!!]